

DETAILS

Address:

Krakow

Phone:

+48 503 129 296

Email:

igor.batko.batko@gmail.com

Date of birth: 23.05.1998

SKILLS

- •••• Communication
- •••• Working in team
- •••• Working under pressure
- •••• Coding
- •••• Adapting and fast learning

IGOR BATKO

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

PROFILE

24 year old man born in Krakow. Witty and ambitious water and winter sports enthusiast. Windsurfing instructor since 2016 and head-instructor for last 2 years. Interested in computers since a child. Began programming few years ago as a hobby and started a front-end bootcamp in September 2021.

Main technologies i worked with:

- -HTML5
- -CSS/SCSS
- -JAVASCRIPT
- -REACT
- -GIT

I am highly open-minded and love to meet new opportunities. I can assure you that I will try my best to bring some value & positive atmosphere to your team. Please check out my portfolio: https://wobcio-portfolio.herokuapp.com/

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Pizzer in Mashgarden Plac Wolnica 10

Apr. 2022 - Present

Math teacher in project - Wirtualny Nauczyciel

Jan. 2021 - Jun. 2021

Windsurfing head-instructor at FunSurf (seasonal)

Jun. 2020 - Sep. 2021

Customer Advisor in ski shop - Adventure Sports

Nov. 2020 - Jun. 2021

Swimming freelance-instructor (few hours per week)

Sep. 2019 - Present

Windsurfing instructor at FunSurf (seasonal)

Jun. 2016 - Sep. 2019

Skiing freelance-instructor (seasonal)

Jan. 2015. - Present

EDUCATION

Kodilla Front-end React Developer bootcamp

Sep 2021- March 2022

AGH Kraków - Electronics and Telecom (1 year)

Sep. 2018 - Jun. 2019

Windsurfing instructor course and practice

May 2016 - Jun. 2016

Ski PZN instructor

Dec. 2014

VIII LO in Krakow

Jan 2014 - 2017

LANGUAGES

Polish: Native

English: B2/C1

CERTIFICATE

of Completion

This is to certify that Igor Batko

Date of birth: 23.05.1998 place of birth: Kraków, PESEL number: 1) 98052302959

1

has successfully completed

Bootcamp Front-end

A 360 hours course, from 27.10.2021 to 02.03.2022 run by Codemy S.A., Legnicka 55F lok. 101. Street, 54-203 Wrocław.

This certificate affirms the abilities in technologies and languages listed below:

HTML, CSS, RWD, Bootstrap, Git, JavaScript ES6, AJAX React, Redux, React Router

The certificate issued pursuant to § 18 act of of the Ordinance of the Minister of Education of 11 January 2012 on continuing education in out-of-school forms (Journal of Laws, item 186).

Wrocław 21.03.2022 r.

No.²⁾ 12046/2022

ul. Leghjcka 55F lok. 101 54-203 Wrocław NIP 8992780056 REGON 363252447

¹⁾ PESEL - personal number. In the case of a person who does not have a PESEL number, enter the name and number of the document confirming their identity.

²⁾ Enter the number from the record of the certificates kept by the continuing education institution, the practical training institution or the vocational training and further training center.

Cover Letter

I have always loved math. Ever since I was a child, solving riddles and calculations brought me joy and satisfaction. I was truly fascinated with it. After finishing high school and not having any idea about what I want to be doing in my life I decided to start getting stem education at AGH. It did not live up to my expectations so I made a decision to quit. Trying to find my calling,I was taking various jobs, most of them as a sports instructor, as I had the necessary experience and certification. During my stay on Hel peninsula, where I used to spend 4-5 months a year as a windsurfing instructor, two of my friends suggested me taking up programming. They were ex-kitesurfing instructors. I decided to give it a go and I fell in love with it straight away. I managed to save up some money for bootcamp and day-to-day living expenses, so I could put all of my focus towards building and expanding my skills. Certainly, it was not easy, but thanks to hard work and discipline I was able to fully understand the topic and gain a solid foundation in IT.

Now I am looking for opportunities do further develop my skills and gain some valuable, hands-on experience dealing with projects. Logical and mathematical thinking are definitely my strengths, and I am able to put in the work to help overcome any challenge. I soak up new information like a sponge and I do not hesitate to ask questions if I am not sure of something. I believe that the internship you offer would be a perfect chance for me to prove how solid of an employee I am as well as show how seriously I think about a career in programming.